const questionsQA = [
  {
    question: "What does the acronym QA mean in software development?",
    answer: ["Quality Analysis", "Quality Assurance", "Quick Assessment"],
    correct: 1,
    wrong: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the main objective of Quality Assurance (QA) in the software development process?",
    answer: [
      "Identify and fix bugs after software release.",
      "Ensure customer requirements are met.",
      "Prevent defects in the development process.",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    wrong: [0, 1],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the main difference between Quality Assurance (QA) and Quality Control (QC)?",
    answer: [
      "QA focuses on preventing defects, while QC focuses on identifying defects.",
      "QA occurs during development while QC occurs after development.",
      "QA is performed by developers while QC is performed by testers.",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    wrong: [1, 2],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What are the key benefits of effectively implementing QA in a software project?",
    answer: [
      "Reduced costs and development time.",
      "Increased customer satisfaction and better company reputation.",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    wrong: [0, 1],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the role of the QA tester in a software development project?",
    answer: [
      "Write code to implement features.",
      "Document customer requirements.",
      "Identify and report bugs during testing.",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    wrong: [0, 1],
  },
  {
    question: "How important is test automation in the QA process?",
    answer: [
      "Automating tests reduces the need for testers.",
      "Automating tests helps you run repetitive tests quickly and efficiently.",
      "Automating testing does not have a significant impact on the QA process.",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    wrong: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is one of the main steps in the Quality Assurance (QA) process in software development?",
    answer: [
      "Implementation of new functionalities.",
      "Customer acceptance testing.",
      "Daily development meetings.",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    wrong: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question: "What is a test plan in the context of Quality Assurance (QA)?",
    answer: [
      "A list of bugs found during testing.",
      "A document that describes the general approach to testing the software.",
      "A final report that confirms that the software is free from defects.",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    wrong: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question: "What does Test-Driven Development (TDD) mean?",
    answer: [
      "Develop software without testing.",
      "Write tests before writing production code.",
      "Carry out testing only after development is complete.",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    wrong: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the difference between white box testing and black box testing?",
    answer: [
      "White box testing tests the external functionality of the software while black box testing tests the internal structure.",
      "White box testing examines the source code, while black box testing does not require internal knowledge of the system.",
      "There is no difference between the two; they are interchangeable terms.",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    wrong: [0, 2],
  },
];

export default questionsQA;
